(Stuart:)Sorry, you want me to take
you to the dentist?
(Sheldon:)Yes. And, now,
I can't make any promises...
(Sheldon:)...but that's the sort of thing that gets a fella
on the list for the number eight friend slot.
(Stuart:)Sheldon, I'm working.
I can't take you to the dentist.
(Stuart:)Also, and I can't stress this enough,
I don't want to take you to the dentist.
(Sheldon:)Can't help a friend out
in a time of need, huh?
(Sheldon:)I see where your therapist
was coming from.
Ooh, ooh. What about we make
your astronaut nickname...
...Howard "Buzz" Wolowitz?
(Howard:)You can't do Buzz. Buzz is taken.
(Raj:)Buzz Lightyear is not real.
(Howard:)No, that's not what I'm talking about.
(Raj:)Well, are you talking about
when he thought he was real?
(Leonard:)No.